export const quizQuestions = [
    {
        id: '1',
        question: "Who is POTUS?",
        answer: "President of United States",
        options: [
            "People of United States", "President of United States", "Parliamentary office to United States"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '2',
        question: "Color of Rose flower?",
        answer: "Red",
        options: [
            "Green", "Blue", "Red"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '3',
        question: "What is INDIA?",
        answer: "Country",
        options: [
            "Country", "Continent", "City"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '4',
        question: "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is",
        answer: "Silver",
        options: [
            "Zinc", "Silver", "Copper"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '5',
        question: "Tsunamis are not caused by",
        answer: "Hurricanes",
        options: [
            "Earthquakes", "Volcanic eruptions", "Hurricanes"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '6',
        question: "Volcanic eruption do not occur in the",
        answer: "Baltic sea",
        options: [
            "Black sea", "Baltic sea", "Caribbean sea"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '7',
        question: "What does VVVF stand for",
        answer: "Variable Voltage Variable Frequency",
        options: [
            "Variable Velocity Variable Fun", "Variable Voltage Variable Frequency", "Variant Voltage Vile Frequency"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '8',
        question: "'OS' computer abbreviation usually means",
        answer: "Operating System",
        options: [
            "Operating System", "Open Software", "Optical Sensor"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '9',
        question: "'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
        answer: "Animation/movie file",
        options: [
            "Animation/movie file", "Audio file", "Image file"
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '10',
        question: "'.MPG' extension refers usually to what kind of file",
        answer: "Animation/movie file",
        options: [
            "Image file", "MS Office document", "Animation/movie file"
        ]
    },
]